

WE CONNECT?

- T.: 654 534 539
- <u>lorenaperezmartinez</u>
- <u>lorenapm</u>

TECH SKILLS















SOFT SKILLS



LORENA PÉREZ MARTÍNEZ

JR. FRONT-END DEVELOPER SENIOR CORPORATE COMMUNICATION

SOBRE MÍ

Who said there is an age to reinvent yourself? After more than 15 years accompanying organizations to communicate with passion, I have turned my professional career around. Now, as a front-end programmer, I am looking forward to facing new challenges and projects where I can add value. I'm just looking for one / my chance. I offer creativity, commitment and motivation.

FORMACIÓN

ADALAB Bootcamp Front-End Developer - Promo M

- Layout: HTNL5, CSS3, CSS Grid, SASS y Bootstrap
- JavaScript (ES6) and basic knowledge of API development.
- · Version control with Git.
- Creation of a SPAs with React.
- Basic knowledge of API developmen and backend: Node IS, Express y SQL
- Slack, GitHub, VS Code, Gulp, Terminal, Linter, Zeplin
- Agile methodologies.

Master economic information and corporate communication

2004 // UCM (Universidad Complutense de Madrid)

Degree in journalism

1999- 2003 // UCM (Universidad Complutense de Madrid)

EXPERIENCIA

SENIOR CORPORATE COMMUNICATION - FREELANCE 2006 - 2021 ||

- Corporate communication projects and eLearning training for companies of very different sizes and sectors, such as Repsol, Mutualidad de la Abogacía, Roche, Asisa, VitalDent, HNA, KPMG, LIRE, etc.
- Some proyects: new shareholder community, corporate websites, blogs, internal and external communication magazines (online and printed), training courses, reports, multimedia content, etc.

EDITOR-IN-CHIEF - COPYWRITER

- 2006-2009 Wolters Kluwer.
- 2004-2005 GBA Información Económica.
- 2003-2004 Netdoctor.

BUSINESS MANAGEMENT

- 1998-1997 Assistant to Operations General Management -Zoppi S.A. (Argentina)
- 1994-1997 Partner Labor S.L. (Argentina)